mashbord.com 2012-09-11

# Mashbord: Privacy Policy

We respect the privacy of all Mashbord.com users are committed to protecting it.

We may collect personal information, including email addresses, when individuals register to use the Mashbord website and services, submit questions, comments or bug reports. We may also, at times, collect our users' IP addresses and information regarding our users' use of our website and services. We may use such IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our website and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Service. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type. Unless required by law, we will not share our users' personal information, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and usage information, except with their consent or in aggregate or anonymous form, with third parties.

In order to offer and provide optimized and personalized services, we use cookies to store and sometimes track information about our users. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive.

Our services give you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. When you first sign up for your Mashbord account, you will have the opportunity to also sign up to receive information/ offers from Mashbord.

Visit your Mashbord Profile settings to edit your profile and other information. When you're signed in, Mashbord page footers will include a link to your account settings. You can delete your Mashbord account by emailing support@mashbord.com with your request to delete your account.

Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. For that reason, we will not collect age information for users under 18 years.

Mashbord reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our blog so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization from the appropriate user(s) to do otherwise.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website or your dealings with this Mashbord, you can send an e-mail, in English, to privacy@mashbord.com

Effective Date: January 1, 2009
